

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

C, C#, Java, Python, PHP, Matlab

Frameworks/Systems

Deen Learning

- TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Data Science

-NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Seaborn, Scikit-Learn

Others

- Ruby on Rails, Laravel

COURSES

- Neural Networks and Deep Learning/ Coursera
- AI for Everyone/Coursera
- Machine Learning Crash Course/Google Developers
- Signal and Image Processing, Deep Learning/ TED University
- Database Design and Programming with SQL/ORACLE
- Machine Learning, Deep Learning/IEEE TURKEY SECTION
- Radar Systems
 Fundamentals/ASELSAN
- DATAI TEAM
 - -Statistics & Python: Basic Statistics Science
 - -Deep Learning and Python: Deep Learning
 - -Machine Learning and Python
 - -Data Visualization
 - -Data Science and Python: Expertise

CONTACT

elif.meseci@outlook.com

linkedin.com/in/elifmeseci/

github.com/elifmeseci

kaggle.com/elifmeseci

REFERENCES

Assist. Prof. Dr. Caner OZCAN CEO, Founder of SimurgAI

4 +90 (370) 418 7277

canerozcan@karabuk.edu.tr

ELIF MESECI

Computer Engineer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I completed my bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering Department at Karabuk University. I worked on Data Science, Data Analysis, Machine Learning, Deep Learning at Karabuk University Computer Engineering Department. My project named Analysis of Panoramic Dental Images with Deep Learning, which I developed with my advisor, received support within the scope of Tubitak 2209 University Students Support Program. Since November 2020, I have been working as an Artificial Intelligence Specialist at SimurgAI, which is located in Karabük University Technology Development Office. I have been working as a Research Assistant at Zonguldak Bülent Ecevit University since February 2022.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Karabuk University | 2021 -

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Karabuk University (GPA- 3.04 / 4.00) | 2016 - 2021

EXPERIENCE

REASECH ASSISTANT | Zonguldak Bulent Ecevit University | Feb 2022-

Department of Computer Engineering

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE SPECIALIST | SimurgAI | Nov 2021-

Use of artificial intelligence and machine learning solutions in solving algorithms for complex problems, evaluation and improvement of the performance of applications developed in the field of artificial intelligence

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE DEVELOPER | SimurgAI | Oct 2020 - Nov 2021

Literature review of related studies and analysis of artificial intelligence algorithms, application of deep learning techniques for image segmentation

SUMMER INTERN | Karabuk University | Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

Data science, data analysis, machine learning and deep learning studies has been conducted.

LABORATORY ASSISTANT | Karabuk University | Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

Student Assistant of CME112-Programming Languages Course

PROJECTS

CARIES DETECTION ON RADIOGRAPHS USING CLASSIC MACHINE LEARNING CLASSIFIERS

SimurgAI | 2021-

Diagnosis of dental caries is a visual method based on clinical and radiographic examination. In radiographic examination, various factors such as irradiation parameters, type of imager, film processing, imaging system, examination conditions, radiographic illusion, training and experience of the observer can affect the accurate detection of carious lesions. Therefore, radiographic diagnosis of dental caries should always be supported by a careful clinical examination. Detection of dental caries is provided by using classical machine learning classifier algorithms in panoramic x-ray images.

ANALYSIS OF PANORAMIC DENTAL IMAGES USING ARTIFICIAL LEARNING TECHNIQUES

SimurgAI | 2020- 2021

As the workload of dentists is too high, treatments cannot be followed regularly, and because of the COVID-19 epidemic and similar epidemic risks in the future, less doctor-patient contact is required, as a solution, artificial intelligence supported dental radiography analysis is performed.

SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTRA ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK RCNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

SimurgAI | 2020 - 2021

In the treatment and diagnosis process of teeth that need to be examined in detail in the field of dental health, bitewing intraoral radiography images are used. It is an ideal diagnostic method for the detection of recurrent caries that cannot be directly seen in the mouth, especially at the interface of small and large molars and under restorations.

CLASSIFICATION OF WRIST IMAGES WITH DEEP LEARNING MODELS

Medathon | 2021

VGG, AlexNet, ResNet were used with 1000 Hand Wrist W-Ray images submitted the under the competition. Transfer Learning methods were used.

PAPERS

B.Y. Tekin, C. Ozcan, A. Pekince, Y. Yasa, A. Karaoglu, S. Cilek, D. Ozdemir, E. Meseci, Tooth Detection and Numbering with Instance Segmentation in Panoramic Radiographs, International Conference on Interdisciplinary Applications of Artificial Intelligence (ICIDAAI), 1st, Online, 21-23 May, 2021.

A. Karaoglu, C. Ozcan, A. Pekince, Y. Yasa, E. Meseci, S. Cilek, Segmentation of Bitewing Intraoral X-Ray Images with Mask R-CNN Deep Learning Model, II. International Artificial Intelligence in Health Congress 2021, SS-125,16-18 Nisan,2021.